http://www.thedailycourier.com/help.html

Today is Thursday, December 10th, 2020
All Classifieds  |  Employment  |   Real Estate  |  Automotive  |   Place a classified ad  |  Subscribe to Daily Courier for $15.00 a month
Help
Search:
Help
Frequently Asked Questions (Help)
Is there a fee for using the Daily Courier website?
When is the Daily Courier published, in print and online?
How often do you publish?
When do you update the Web site?
Why should I subscribe to the Daily Courier?
How will the Daily Courier help me save money?
What online content is available for free?
What online content is available only with a membership?
How can I start a subscription for home delivery and/or a membership for online?
What can I do if I have a question about my subscription bill or delivery service?
Your Web site does not display properly on my computer. What do I do?
What's the deadline to place a classified ad?
How can I get a letter to the editor in the paper?
Can I reprint anything that is in the Daily Courier or on the Daily Courier website?
How can I order a photo that appeared in the paper?
How can I get a back issue of the Daily Courier?
How will my personal information be used?
How do I stop my paper temporarily while on vacation?
How can I place an engagement, wedding, anniversary or birth announcement?
How do I get an obituary published?
How do I get information published about my business?
Who do I contact with a story idea or news tip?
Where can I recycle my newspapers?
Where is the Daily Courier office located?
What number do I call to contact:
Where can I get more information?
Is there a fee for using the Daily Courier website?
top
If you are a home delivery subscriber of the Daily Courier, online membership is included. If you would like to have online access only, you may purchase an online membership.
Click here for more information.
When is the Daily Courier published, in print and online?
top
The Daily Courier print edition goes to press around 11:55 AM Tuesday through Friday. We want to give our readers the very best service possible. Our commitment to you is that the Daily Courier be delivered to your home or office by 5 PM in a dry, readable condition. If for any reason you do not receive your paper or are dissatisfied with your service, call customer service at (541) 474-3702, 8 AM to 5 PM Monday, 8 AM to 6:30 PM Tuesday through Friday, 2 PM to 11 PM Saturday and 6 AM to 10 AM Sunday.
The Daily Courier online edition is constantly updated during the day to give our members the most up-to-date breaking news and information.
How often do you publish?
top
We publish the Daily Courier print edition every Tuesday through Friday afternoon and Sunday morning. The only holidays we do not print a newspaper is Thanksgiving, Christmas Day and New Year's Day.
When do you update the Web site?
top
The Daily Courier online edition is updated during the day to give our members the most up-to-date breaking news and information.
Why should I subscribe to the Daily Courier?
top
When you subscribe to home delivery of the Daily Courier print edition, you'll not only receive the list of items below, you'll also automatically receive membership to the Web site content.
Subscribe
and receive: Local & National News, Local & National Sports, Classifieds, WeeksWorth TV Magazine, Business page, Entertainment, Recipes and Food page, Healthy Living, Home & Garden, Shopping Inserts and much much more! This doesn't include all you get with your online membership!
How will the Daily Courier help me save money?
top
You'll find hundreds of bargains and sales in the Daily Courier, both in print and online. Browse the many classified ads, clip coupons for your local grocery store to help save on your grocery bill or learn about a blowout sale at your favorite store. We guarantee that the money you may save from information in the paper will pay for your subscription many times over.
What online content is available for free?
top
National news, local resource links and information, stock quotes, videos, web cams and some breaking news stories.
What online content is available only with a membership?
top
Local news, local sports, obituaries, engagement, wedding & anniversary announcements, police reports, local entertainment, letters to the editor and much more. Additional items will be added on a continuous basis.
How can I start a subscription for home delivery and/or a membership for online?
top
Visit the circulation section of our Web site.
What can I do if I have a question about my subscription bill or delivery service?
top
Call our customer service department at (541) 474-3702.
Your Web site does not display properly on my computer. What do I do?
top
Check to be certain your Java Script is enabled. Also check that cookies is enabled. The Daily Courier treats the handling of your personal information very seriously. Please see our
Privacy Policy Statement
.
What's the deadline to place a classified ad?
top
• For Tuesday: Mon., 12 noon
• For Wednesday: Tues., 12 noon
• For Thursday: Wed., 12 noon
• For Friday: Thu., 12 noon
• For Sunday: Fri., 12 noon
For holiday deadlines call (541) 474-3711.
Please keep in mind, If you're placing a garage sale ad, you'll want to run the ad the day before the sale. So for example, if your sale is Saturday, you'll want to place the ad by noon Thursday so your ad will be in Friday's paper.
To place your classified ad, call (541) 474-3711, visit our office or
place your ad online here
.
How can I get a letter to the editor in the paper
top
The Daily Courier runs original letters from readers. For verification, all letters must be accompanied by the name, address and telephone number of the author, although we don't print addresses or phone numbers. Letters should not exceed 250 words and may be edited for purposes of brevity, clarity or avoiding legal problems. You can
submit a letter to the editor here
or mail to Daily Courier, Letter to the Editor, P.O. Box 1468, Grants Pass, OR 97528.
Can I reprint anything that is in the Daily Courier or on the Daily Courier website?
top
Content on our Web site and in the newspaper are copyrighted. To request permission to reprint an article, write a letter explaining how it will be used and send your request to: Editor, c/o Daily Courier, P.O. Box 1468, Grants Pass, OR 97528.
How can I order a photo that appeared in the paper?
top
Reprints of published Daily Courier photos may be purchased. To obtain a print, submit a dated clipping or photocopy with a check mailed to Daily Courier Photo Dept., P.O. Box 1468, Grants Pass, OR 97528 or visit our office. Prices are as follows: 8"x10" full color print for $20 or a high resolution jpeg e-mailed to you for $10.
How can I get a back issue of the Daily Courier?
top
Generally, we have a few copies of each day's paper for the past year in stock. They are available at the counter in our front lobby. The cost is 75¢. If you would like a newspaper mailed to you, it is $5.00 each. Please call (541) 474-3700 or stop by our office.
How will my personal information be used?
top
Please see our
Privacy Policy Statement
.
How do I stop my paper temporarily while on vacation?
top
If you let us know when you'll be gone, we'll temporarily stop delivery of your newspaper. You can choose one of the following options: 1) Vacation Donation: your paper will be donated to the Newspapers in Education (NIE) program or 2) Vacation Pak: we'll hold your papers while you're gone and deliver them when you return or you can have your account credited.
How can I place an engagement, wedding, anniversary or birth announcement?
top
Forms outlining the information needed to publish news of engagements, weddings, anniversaries and births are available in the Daily Courier lobby or by
clicking here
. These announcements are free! All of the above (excluding births) are announced in Sunday's paper. To qualify for the anniversary announcement, you must be celebrating a milestone anniversary starting at the 50th anniversary (then 55, 60, 65, etc.). Photographs are published with Wedding and Anniversary announcements. They must be clear, sharp prints, black & white or color. We cannot publish announcements received more than one year after the event. For more information call (541) 474-3815 or
news@thedailycourier.com
.
How do I get an obituary published?
top
The Daily Courier prints death notices of residents or former residents of our circulation area. For more information on free death notices, contact Valerie Smith in the newsroom, (541) 474-3823 or send an e-mail to
news@thedailycourier.com
. To place a paid obituary notice or memorial ad, call Tamara Stuebing in our Advertising Department, (541) 474-3714 or e-mail
obits@thedailycourier.com
for more information.
How do I get information published about my business?
top
The Daily Courier publicizes local business news every Sunday in the Business Buzz column on the business page. Events that are eligible include new business openings, a move to a new location by an existing business, major expansions, employee promotions or new hires in management, major industry awards and business closures. Eligible entries will be published on a first-come, first-served basis. If you have something you think would qualify for the column, you can submit a
Business Buzz form
here or pick one up in our lobby.
Who do I contact with a story idea or news tip?
top
The Daily Courier welcomes information about news events or persons involved in newsworthy activities. If you have a story idea, please contact our city editor at (541) 474-3716 or e-mail to
news@thedailycourier.com
.
Where can I recycle my newspapers?
top
Residents within the city of Grants Pass or urban growth boundaries have curbside recycling service. If you do not have a recycle box or cart, you may contact the sanitation company for your area (Allied Waste Services, (541) 479-3371 or Southern Oregon Sanitation, (541) 479-5335). There are recycling centers at both sanitation companies (Allied Waste Services, 1920 NW Washington Blvd., Grants Pass and Southern Oregon Sanitation, 1381 Redwood Ave., Grants Pass). You can also recycle at the Josephine County Transfer & Recycling Center (1749 Merlin Rd.) and the Kerby Transfer Station (905 Kerby Mainline Rd., Kerby).
Where is the Daily Courier office located?
top
The Daily Courier offices are located at 409 S.E. 7th St., Grants Pass, Oregon 97526 (corner of 7th & "J" Streets).
What number do I call to contact:
The direct front line is (541) 474-3700.
Where can I get more information?
top
You can email
webmaster@thedailycourier.com
and we'll do our best to answer your questions or address your concerns.
Send questions, comments or suggestions about this site to comments@thedailycourier.com.
This site Copyright © 2020. Grants Pass Daily Courier / Courier Publishing Company.
Privacy Policy | Terms of Use
409 S.E. 7th Street, Grants Pass, OR 97526-3003 | P.O. Box 1468, Grants Pass, OR 97528-0330
Phone: (541) 474-3700 | Toll-Free in Oregon: (800) 228-0457.
Office Hours: Mon. - Fri. 8 a.m - 5 p.m.
